(ﾅﾚｰｼｮﾝ)
＜ディアンヌの神器を得るため➡
In order to retrieve Diane's Sacred Treasure, the group enters the Byzel Fight Festival.
バイゼルの喧嘩祭りに
参加した一行＞
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)えい！ うふっ｡
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)ノー！
＜ それぞれが
それぞれの思惑を巡らせて➡
The festival begins to heat up as
everyone focuses on their own goals.
祭りは
更にヒートアップしてゆく＞
Capt—no, wait, Meliodaz! Good luck!
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)団長… じゃなくて
メリオダフ ファイト～！
B-Baan! If you lose and get humiliated, I'll tell Elaine!
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)バ… バーン！
あんまりぶざまに負けたら➡
エレインに言いつけるぞ！
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)あっ そうだ｡
Oh, that's right!
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)ん!?
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)ｴﾘｻﾞﾍﾞｽも応援しなよ｡➡
You should cheer too, Elizabeth!
It's all right! No one will notice you.
大丈夫｡
周りには気付かれないから｡
(ｴﾘｻﾞﾍﾞｽ)えっ ええ…｡
(ﾗﾌﾞﾍﾙﾑ)それでは 喧嘩開始～！
O-Okay...
Well then, let the fight begin!
(ﾊﾞﾝ)
もうちょい広い方がいいのによぉ｡
It would've been nice if the ring were a bit bigger.
(ﾒﾘｵﾀﾞｽ)にししっ｡
(ﾊﾞﾝ)なんだよ 急に？
What's wrong all of a sudden?
そんなに
俺とやるのが楽しいのか～？
Are you that excited to fight me?
I was just reminded of something...
昔を思い出したんだよ｡ ちょうど
このくらいの広さだったな｡
It was about this size back then as well.
昔～？ 教えろよぉ｡
Back then? Tell me already!
な～に すぐ思い出すって｡
(ﾊﾞﾝ)あっ｡
Don't worry, you'll get it right away!
ほっ！
ぐはっ！
あっ 思い出した～！
Ah, now I remember!
((随分 厳重な造りだなぁ))
This place sure is high-security.
(衛兵)((当然です｡
４年前 妖精王の森を➡
Of course it is!
This is the man sentenced to die
全焼させた大罪人ですから))
for the great sin of burning down the Fairy King's Forest four years ago!
But he's still alive after being executed 33 times, isn't he?
((でも ３３回 死刑執行されても
まだ生きてんだろ？))
Correct.
(衛兵)((そうです｡
首をはねようと 炎で焼こうとも➡
We've tried beheading and burning, but nothing's worked...
ことごとく｡
あ… あの男は人間じゃない))
H-He's not human!
I see. What a coincidence.
((ふ～ん 奇遇だな))
(衛兵)((はっ？))
((開けてくれ))
Open it up.
(ﾊﾞﾝ)
((ん？ ま～た死刑のお時間か？➡
Time for another execution?
もう めんどいから動かね～ぞ｡➡
What a pain. I'm not moving an inch.
If you're gonna do it, just do it here.
用があるなら ここで済ませろよ))
((バタン(扉の開閉音)))
((あっ？➡
A brat?
ガキじゃねぇか))
((不死身のバン 出ろ))
Undead Ban. We're leaving.
((はっ？ 話聞いてたか？
このガキんちょ))
Huh? Didn't you hear what I just said, you brat?
((力ずくで出すしかねぇか))
Guess I'll have to bust you out by force.
((やってみろよ｡
だが ガキでも…))
Go ahead and try.
Even if you're a brat, I won't go easy—
You really did bust me out!
((ぺっ！))
((かははっ！➡
マジで出されちまった～))
((まずは 俺の１勝… だな))
Guess the first round goes to me, huh?
Let's do that again!
If you want to continue,
you'll have to come with me.
((続きがしたきゃ
ここを出て 俺と組めよ))
A one-hit KO right off the bat!
(ﾗﾌﾞﾍﾙﾑ)開始早々 一撃決着～！
(ﾊﾞﾝ)いくぜ！
くっ！
Here I come!
はあ～～！
ドカッ ドカッ ドカッ ドカッ…
Take this!
なんの！
ドドォーン！
＜ これは いまだ
人と 人ならざるものの世界が➡
This is a tale of humans and beings from other worlds.
分かたれてはいなかった
古の物語＞
It is a story of ancient times.
＜聖騎士は かつて
他の三つの種族と共に➡
Long ago, the Holy Knights fought alongside three tribes to seal away the Demon Clan.
魔神族を闇に葬った＞
＜聖戦と呼ばれたその戦いは➡
It was known as the Holy War, and memory of it has long left the minds of the people.
時を経て 人々の記憶から
消えてなくなった＞
＜ だが 今再び 聖戦が叫ばれる＞
However, a new Holy War has begun.
＜七つの大罪を葬り去れと＞
The battle to banish the Seven Deadly Sins unto oblivion.
I'll shout out a love that doesn't cease to resound
nariyamanu ai o sakebu yo
I continue to take everything in my arms
subete o daite koko ni irun da
For that's where our light lies
hikari wa soko ni aru yo
With unyielding emotions in tow,
yuzurenai omoi o kakete
I'll be the one to live on the edge of my hopes
kibou no hate o boku wa ikiru yo
A dream connects me to you
yume o tsunaida kimi to
A beginning will someday be born from our own hands
hajimari o itsuka bokura no te de umidasun da yo
And with how kind you are, I'm sure your voice will be able to change the world
yasashii kimi no koe mo kitto sekai o kaerareru
Since people can't totally stand up all on their own,
dare mo hitori kiri ja tachiagare yashinai kara
we'll reach out our hands to one another
tagai ni te o nobashite
and head for a tomorrow that surpasses all limits
kagiri no koeta ashita e
I'll shout out a love that doesn't cease to resound
nariyamanu ai o sakebu yo
As we begin to butt heads and get to know one another better,
butsukariatte wakariaun da
we'll create a path of light.
hikari o tsukuridasu yo
Guided by my tenacity,
akiramenu omoi o kakete
I'll be the one to live on the edge of my hopes
kibou no hate o boku wa ikiru yo
A dream connects me with you
yume o tsunai da kimi to
Episode 11
The Sentiment of Many Years
(観客)あ… あのバーンってヤツ
死んだんじゃ…｡
Th-That Baan guy must be dead!
(観客)
っていうか これ もはや 喧嘩か？
Is this even considered a fight anymore?
He's completely fine!
ピンピンしてる！
So these are the Deadly Sins!
(ﾊｳｻﾞｰ･心の声)
≪これが 七つの大罪…｡➡
どっちも化け物すぎんだろ≫
They're both beyond monsters!
ドゴン！
かはっ！
ふん！
バキッ！
Whoa! Are they both down?!
(ﾗﾌﾞﾍﾙﾑ)
お～っと 両者ともダウンか～!?
うんにゃ～｡
にゃろう やりやがったな｡
Bastard, you've really done it, huh?
(ﾊﾞﾝ)はははっ！ そ～れっと｡
Upsy-daisy.
(ﾗﾌﾞﾍﾙﾑ)ど… どうなってる～!?
バーンの負っていた傷が➡
Wh-What's going on?!
Baan's wounds have completely healed!
きれいさっぱり消えた！
バキッ！
Th-Those two are insane!
こ… こいつら イカレてる｡
(ﾎｰｸ)エール 残り僅かだよ～！
Get your ale before it runs out!
≫いらっしゃ～い！
はははっ！ 体が 超軽いっすわ｡
Welcome!
My body's as light as a feather!
バキッ！
がはっ！➡
ってぇ～…
歯が折れちまったろうが｡
You made me lose a tooth!
なんつって｡
Just kidding.
Hey, King!
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)ねえ キング｡
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)うん｡
Yeah.
徐々に 団長が バンの動きを
捉えきれなくなってる｡
Little by little, Captain's losing
his ability to keep up with Ban.
団長のスタミナが
減ってるってこと？
You mean Captain's running out of stamina?
When Captain started getting sluggish, Ban suddenly became more agile!
団長の動きが鈍くなった直後➡
バンの動きに鋭さが増した｡
えっ？
どういうことですか？
What do you mean?
Snatch
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)バンの魔力｢強奪｣は
スピードやパワーといった➡
Ban's power, Snatch, can take away speed and power—it can rob physical abilities!
身体能力を奪うことが
できるんです｡
なんの！
くっ！
Take this!
Meliodaz turns around and smashes Baan back and forth like a rag doll!
(ﾗﾌﾞﾍﾙﾑ)
メリオダフが一転 バーンを➡
ボロ布のごとく たたきつける！➡
なんというパワーだ！
Such power!
This feeling of having Cap'n's
power coursing through me...
Physical Hunt
(ﾊﾞﾝ)団ちょのが
俺の中に流れ込む この感覚…➡
この高揚感！
あっ…｡
This ecstasy!
(ﾊﾞﾝ)どんだけ 団ちょのパワーが
乗ったか➡
I wonder how much of Cap'n's
power has been added to mine!
試させてくれよ！
Let me test it out!
ボキッ！
ドゴン！
ふっ！
がはぁ～！
(ﾊﾞﾝ)マジかよ｡ 団ちょの力は
どんだけ底なしなんだぁ？➡
You've gotta be kidding me.
Just how much strength lies within you, Cap'n?
かっかっ！ よし 決めた｡
All right, I've decided.
ギブアップをか？
ちょっとやそっと➡
Decided to give up?
Well, I don't think we can end this fight
スピードやパワーを
奪ったところで➡
just by stealing a little speed or strength here and there, so...
そう簡単に
決着はつきそうにねぇしな｡
I'll take it all!
全部もらう｡
んんっ！
バキッ バキッ バキッ バキッ…
End it right here and now!
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)
一気に カタをつけちゃえ～！
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)
力を奪い取れば バンの勝利｡➡
Ban will win if he can steal all of Captain's strength.
その前にしとめれば 団長の勝利｡
But Captain will win if he can finish it before then!
うまかったぜ 団ちょ｡
That was delicious, Cap'n!
(ﾗﾌﾞﾍﾙﾑ)お～っと
これは どうしたことだ!?➡
Whoa, what's going on?!
一方的に 攻撃を
仕掛けていたはずのメリオダフ➡
Meliodaz ran out of strength after a ferocious offensive!
力尽きた～！
Lord King, what happened to Lord Meliodas?
キング様｡
メリオダス様に 一体 何が？
Ban has completely robbed
Captain of his physical abilities.
団長の身体能力を
バンが 全て奪ったんです｡
団ちょとの
楽し～い殴り合いの時間も➡
The happy and fun brawl with the Cap'n is about to come to an end...
そろそろ
終わりに近づいてまいりました｡
What would you like to do?
いかがしましょう？
≫(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)バン！➡
Ban!
これ以上 団長に何かしたら
僕が許さないよ！➡
If you do anything more to Captain, I'll never forgive you!
もう 絶交だから！
I'll cut all ties with you, too!
外野は黙ってろ｡
The audience needs to shut up.
I'm the one winning this fight.
勝負に勝ったのは 俺なんだ｡
にししっ…｡
You can keep on dreaming.
寝ぼけたこと言ってんじゃねぇよ｡
勝つのは俺だぜ｡
I'm the one who's gonna win!
ひひっ！ やっぱ 団ちょと俺って
最高に気が合うよなぁ｡
I knew it! Cap'n and I really do go well together!
Well then, allow me to deliver one final blow!
それじゃあ
最後に一発 いかせてもらうぜぇ｡
バン様を止めて！
このままじゃ メリオダス様が…｡
Please stop Lord Ban!
If this keeps going, Lord Meliodas will—
This fight is gonna go to Captain!
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)この勝負 団長の勝ちだよ｡
どういうこと？
What do you mean?
団長はね やられたふりをして➡
Captain's just pretending to be defeated to bait Ban into delivering his most powerful blow.
バンの最大パワーのパンチを
｢全反撃｣で はね返すつもりだよ｡
Then he'll reflect it back with Full Counter.
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)それは無理さ｡
えっ？
That's impossible.
ごめん ディアンヌ｡
団長の魔力で はね返せるのは➡
Sorry, Diane.
Captain's special power can only
reflect direct special power attacks.
あくまで
直接攻撃の魔力のみなんだ｡
So it's useless against something like an ordinary punch.
だから
ただのパンチには 無力なんだよ｡
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)
うそ～!? じゃあ なんで団長は？
No way!
Then what is Captain doing?!
おいらにも分からないよ｡
Even I don't know!
If you survive this, tell me how it feels!
生きてたら
あとで 感想聞かせてくれよな｡
俺と団ちょ
二人のパワーを乗せた拳の味をよ｡
I want to know how the fist with our combined powers tastes!
メリオダス様～！
Lord Meliodas!
はあっ！
ドォーーン！
He really finished him off!
(ﾊｳｻﾞｰ)
マジで とどめ刺しやがった！➡
あいつら 仲間じゃねぇのか？
Aren't they comrades?
No way... Lord Meliodas...
やだ… メリオダス様…｡
メリオダス様～！
Lord Meliodas!
Shh! Elizabeth, you can't be so loud!
しっ！ エリザベス ダメだろ｡
(ﾗﾌﾞﾍﾙﾑ)あっ｡
(ﾊｳｻﾞｰ)あれ？
Wha—
The only person left in the ring is Meliodaz! Where did Baan go?!
(ﾗﾌﾞﾍﾙﾑ)おろ？ リングの上には
メリオダフ ただ一人｡➡
バーンは いずこ？
Look over there.
ほれ あそこ｡
(ﾗﾌﾞﾍﾙﾑ)あっ？
ごふっ…｡
Then I guess... this means...
(ﾗﾌﾞﾍﾙﾑ)
これは その～… ということは？
It's my win!
俺の勝ち｡ にししっ！
(ﾗﾌﾞﾍﾙﾑ)勝者 メリオダフ！
(観客たち)わあ～！
Winner, Meliodaz!
Hell yeah! Sold a whole barrel before the semifinals!
いよ～っし！
準決勝前に ひと樽 完売｡
I always knew I was the best at this!
さすが 俺｡ 俺 最高～！
D-Diane...
ディ… ディアンヌ｡
うん…｡
Yeah...
For a split second, I thought I saw something strange.
瞬きをする一瞬 おいら
妙なものを見たような気が…｡
ううん
僕には はっきり見えたよ｡➡
Yeah... I was able to see it clearly.
バンは 確かに 渾身の一撃を
団長に打ち込んだ｡➡
Ban hit Captain with everything he had.
But at the same time, Captain's hand crushed Ban's wrist.
でも 同時に 団長の手は➡
バンの手首を
握り潰していたんだ｡➡
そして 次の瞬間…｡
And then, in the next instant...
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)
バンの体は吹き飛ばされていて…｡
Ban's body was blown away.
あの姿の団長
前にも見たことがある｡
I've seen Captain like that once before...
I don't know why, but it makes me feel uneasy.
なんだろう…
すごく不安な感じがするの｡
≪額に 黒い紋様？≫
A black mark on his forehead...
Isn't that the same as Dalmary—
≪それって
ダルマリーのときの？≫
Yo, guys!
よう お前ら｡ なんだよ？
そろって シケた顔しちゃって｡
What's going on?
Looking all gloomy like that...
Are you feeling okay already?
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)体は もう平気なの？
見てのとおり｡
Yep, as you can see!
バンをぶっ倒した途端 元に戻った｡
As soon as I blew Ban away, I returned to normal!
じゃあ 倒す前に動いてたのは➡
Then how was he able to move before Ban was defeated?
どゆこと？
どうしたんだ？ ディアンヌ｡
What's wrong, Diane?
わっ…｡
珍しく緊張してんのか？
Are you nervous for once?
Your next opponent does look tough...
次の相手も
なかなか手ごわそうだしな｡
(ﾊｳｻﾞｰ)うっし！
あんなもん見せられたら➡
All right!
Watching a fight like that has got me all fired up!
こっちも
俄然 テンション上がるわなぁ｡
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)
ああ～ 大変！ 早く行かなきゃ｡➡
Oh no, I have to get going!
はい 団長｡
Here, Captain!
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)頑張れ マトローナ！
Do your best, Matrona!
ディアンヌ
くれぐれも むちゃしないでね！
Please don't push yourself, Diane!
Yep!
きゃあ～！
メリオダフ！
Meliodaz!
(ｸﾞﾘｱﾓｰﾙ)ベロニカ様｡
(ﾍﾞﾛﾆｶ)あっ｡ いたかい？
Lady Veronica.
Did you find her?
I've searched the area, but there are no signs of her.
(ｸﾞﾘｱﾓｰﾙ)会場を
くまなく捜しましたが どこにも｡
(ﾍﾝﾄﾞﾘｸｾﾝ)((七つの大罪を
バイゼルの町に おびき出します))
We will lure the Sins to the town of Byzel.
How?
(ｸﾞﾘｱﾓｰﾙ)((どうやって？))
(ﾍﾝﾄﾞﾘｸｾﾝ)((ディアンヌの神器を➡
We'll use Diane's Sacred Treasure as the extra prize in the festival.
祭りの副賞にするのです))
(ﾍﾞﾛﾆｶ)((じゃあ 妹は…))
Then my sister—
((エリザベス様は
必ず 連中のそばにいます))
Princess Elizabeth will definitely be with them.
(ﾍﾞﾛﾆｶ)エリーは いるよ➡
Ellie is here.
この会場のどこかに｡
(ｸﾞﾘｱﾓｰﾙ)ベロニカ様…｡
Somewhere in this venue.
Lady Veronica...
(ﾍﾞﾛﾆｶ)ヘンドリクセンに
言われたからじゃない｡
And not just because Hendriksen said so.
あの子を感じるんだ｡
(ｸﾞﾘｱﾓｰﾙ)もう一度➡
I can feel her presence.
I will go and look once more.
捜してまいります｡
頼んだよ｡
Thank you.
おにいさん
そろそろ決めてくれるかい？
Could you hurry up and decide, sir?
喧嘩祭り 準決勝
始まっちゃうんだよね｡
The semifinals have started already.
The Crime in the Sleeping Forest.
(ｱﾗﾝ)｢眠れる森の罪｣… これは
前に読んだことありますね｡➡
I've read this before.
｢キケンな男｣も
気になるタイトルだ｡➡
Dangerous Man is an interesting title too.
ん？ これは…｡
This is...
Dammit, I can't believe myself...
(ﾊﾞﾝ)くそ～ 抜かったぁ｡
俺としたことが 団ちょの切り札を
すっかり忘れてたぜ～｡
I totally forgot about Cap'n's trump card.
つぅか ありゃなんだ？
Seriously, what was that?
んなことより重ぇよ｡ 自分で歩け｡
Hey, you're heavy! Why don't you walk by yourself?
つれねぇこと言うなよ 師匠～｡
Don't be so cold, Master Pig.
甘えん坊か お前は！
What are you, a spoiled brat?
｢身体狩り｣のあとは 反動で➡
My body feels so heavy after using Physical Hunt.
体が めっちゃ重ったるいんだよぉ｡
ん？ プゴップゴッ… におうな｡
I smell something.
(ﾊﾞﾝ)残飯か？
違ぇよ！
Leftovers?
No!
こりゃあ 嵐が来んぜ｡
There's a storm brewing.
(ﾗﾌﾞﾍﾙﾑ)準決勝 一組目
喧嘩開始だ～！
Fight one of the semifinals, begin!
(ﾗﾌﾞﾍﾙﾑ)お～っと
ハウザー なんという紳士ぶり｡➡
Whoa, Hauser! What a gentleman!
He let Matrona know that her button was undone!
マトローナの外れたボタンを
さりげなく教えてあげた～！➡
But he receives a hail of boos from the crowd!
しかし
一部の客からは 猛烈なヤジ！
目のやり場に困って
喧嘩になんねぇの！
I can't fight if there's
a distraction right in front of me!
(ﾗﾌﾞﾍﾙﾑ)見た目によらず
ハウザー 純情か！
Despite his looks, does Hauser actually have a pure heart?
Well, this is what I'm used
to looking like all the time...
まあ
いつも 僕 こんな感じだけど｡
(ﾊｳｻﾞｰ)｢ライジングトルネード｣！
Rising Tornado
Rising Tornado!
わっ… こんなの もろにくらったら
ひとたまりもないよ｡
I'll be in trouble if I take a direct hit from that!
よく分かってるじゃねぇか｡ だが！
Looks like you understand!
However...
力を抜いて 俺に身を任せろ｡
気持ちいいぜ？➡
Quit struggling and leave it to me!
It'll feel amazing!
空を飛ぶような感覚でイケるぜ！
You'll feel like you're flying through the sky!
That guy is amazing!
あいつ すげぇな｡
スケベ発言 連発だぞ｡
So many perverted comments in a row!
(ﾊｳｻﾞｰ)ぐわっ！ ち… 違っ…｡
Th-That's not—
Is that true?
そうなの？
断じて違う！
Hell no!
I just don't like hurting women, that's all!
俺は 女を傷つけるのが
好きじゃねぇだけだ｡
どんなに強かろうがな｡
No matter how strong they are!
(ﾗﾌﾞﾍﾙﾑ)
お～っと マトローナ 防戦一方！
Whoa! Matrona finds herself on the defensive!
しかたねぇ｡
あんまり 女を追い詰めるまねは➡
Guess there's no other way.
I didn't want to force a woman into anything, but...
したくなかったんだが｡ ふっ！
あっ！
(ﾗﾌﾞﾍﾙﾑ)なんと マトローナの
左右に 竜巻が発生した！➡
What?! Two twisters appear on each side of Matrona!
更に 後ろはなし｡➡
And she's backed to the edge of the ring! She's cornered!
追い詰められた～！
まずい！
No!
Whether you try to jump up high or hunker down low,
上に跳ぼうが 下にかがもうが➡
竜巻は
地面をえぐり 空に巻き上げる！
the twisters will hug the
ground and rise to the skies!
あ～ん！
チェックメイト！
Checkmate!
パシン！
あっ…｡
なっ！ うそだろ？
さっき これをくらったら➡
No way!
Back then you said it'd be bad if you took—
ひとたまりもねぇって… どわっ！
借り物の服だから
傷つけたくなかったの｡ もう！
I borrowed these clothes,
so I didn't want them to be damaged!
Jeez.
(ﾊｳｻﾞｰ)面白ぇ…｡
Interesting...
こいつは
久々に マジになれそうだぜ｡
Guess I can go all out for once.
If you don't want to die, run.
死にたくねぇなら逃げろ｡
(ﾊｳｻﾞｰ)｢ワール･ショック｣‼
Whirl Shock!
Whirl Shock!!
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)きゃあ！
ディアンヌ！
Diane!
ふわぁ～ びっくりした｡
That scared me...
I'm not done yet!
(ﾗﾌﾞﾍﾙﾑ)一体 何が
起きているのか!? 審判も退散！
What's going on?! The referee needs to get away!
Super Cyclone!!
(ﾊｳｻﾞｰ)
俺の作る最強の嵐の味はどうだ!?
How does my strongest storm taste?!
This is crazy! I can barely see inside.
こりゃすげぇ｡
中が ほとんど見えねぇ｡
このままじゃ ディアンヌは…｡
At this rate, Diane will—
If you let your feet off the ground for even a moment, it's over.
一度でも
足が宙に浮いたら終わりだ｡
ま… まあ 俺なら耐えきるな｡
I-I'm sure I'd be able to hold my ground!
吹っ飛べ！
ぐっ… ああっ！
Fly!
俺の勝ちだ～！
This fight is over!
きゃあ～！
Heavy Metal
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)｢重金属｣！
Heavy Metal!
ドスン！
ぐわぁ～！
こ… これは
ハ… ハウザー 完全ダウン！➡
Th-This is...?!
H-Hauser is completely down and out!
よって 準決勝 一組目
勝者は マトローナ！
The winner of the first semifinals fight is Matrona!
あっ！ だ… 大丈夫？
か… 完敗だぜ｡
A-Are you alright?
I-It's my utter defeat.
つい 僕も本気になっちゃって…｡
ごめんね｡
I lost my self-control and got serious, sorry.
A member of the Seven
Deadly Sins took me seriously...
七つの大罪に
本気 出してもらえたんだ｡
I-I'm honored.
光栄だぜ｡
えっ!? え… え～っと➡
Eh? I-I'm just a girl who happened to be in the area.
僕は
ただの通りすがりの女の子で…｡
(ﾊｳｻﾞｰ)ははっ… 無理あんだろ｡
何やら いい雰囲気だな｡
Yeah, right...
They seem to be in a good mood.
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)ディアンヌ！
早く その男から離れるんだ！
Diane! Get away from that man right now!
あん もう！
(ﾊｳｻﾞｰ)｢ディアンヌ｣… やはり…｡
Ugh, jeez!
Diane... I knew it!
ガン！
ぐわっ！ 待ってくれ｡
Wait!
ほんとに ごめんね｡
あっ…｡
I'm really sorry.
I don't believe this.
(ﾀｲｽﾞｰ)信じられねぇ…｡
聖騎士を倒す人間が➡
To think a human exists who can defeat a Holy Knight...
この世にいるなんて｡
(ｹｲﾝ)うしゃしゃ｡
世の中は
広いようで狭いもんじゃよ｡
This world's so big, yet so small, too.
Now it's time for me to confirm that.
今から
それを確かめるとするかの｡
And now, the second semifinal fight!
(ﾗﾌﾞﾍﾙﾑ)では 準決勝 二組目
メリオダフ対ケイン！
Meliodaz versus Cain!
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)団長 頑張ってね｡
Captain, do your best!
お気をつけて｡
任しとけ｡
Please be careful!
Leave it to me!
Avenge my loss as well!
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)おいらの敵も取ってね｡
自分でやれ｡
Do it yourself.
(観客)期待してるぞ チビッ子！
(観客)また すげぇの見せてくれ！
We're counting on you, shorty!
Show us something amazing again!
(観客)じいさんも負けんな！
(観客)あんな子供に負けるなよ！
Don't lose, gramps!
You gotta beat a kid like him!
(観客)どっちも頑張れ～！
Do your best, both of you!
You sure do resemble him...
それにしても よう似ておるわい｡
その顔を見たとき
まさかとは思うたが➡
When I first saw your face, I thought it was possible,
メリオダフという名を聞いて
それが確信に変わった｡
but once I heard your name, Meliodaz, I knew for sure.
ん？
(ｹｲﾝ)お前さん➡
Hmm?
You're Meliodas's son, are you not?
メリオダスの息子じゃな？
うんにゃ｡
Nope.
メリオダスは 俺だけど｡
I'm Meliodas.
どえぇぇ～!? バカを言え！➡
Wh-Wh-Wh-What?!
Yeah, right! How could a little
midget kid like you be Meliodas?
メリオダスが お前さんのような
小僧なわけあるか！
Shh! I'm trying to lay low
right now for various reasons.
しぃ～！ 今だけ
訳あって 名前 伏せてんだから｡
もし あやつが 今 生きておったら
三十路過ぎの青年になっとるわい｡
Even if he was alive, he'd bce in his thirties by now!
そんなこと言われてもなぁ｡
Look, believe it or not...
わしを覚えておらん時点で
やはり信じ難いが｡
I find it hard to believe you since you don't remember who I am.
Well, sorry about that.
うん 悪いけど｡
もし 本当に お前さんが
わしの知るメリオダスならば…｡
If you really are the Meliodas that I know...
お前を 絶対に許しはせん！
I'll never forgive you!
That crest... It's Danafor's.
あの紋章 ダナフォールの…｡
My father told me about it before.
≪父上が 一度だけ話してくれた➡
The kingdom where I was born...
私の生まれ故郷≫
Gramps, you're...?
じいさん あんた…｡
なぜ 王国を滅ぼした!?
Why did you destroy the kingdom?!
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)直撃だ！
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)団長！
A direct hit!
Captain!
Why did you kill the people?!
なぜ 人々を殺した!?
(ﾗﾌﾞﾍﾙﾑ)お～っと メリオダフ
ケインの不思議な技になす術なし｡
Whoa! Meliodaz is defenseless
against Cain's mysterious powers!
What are you doing, Captain?!
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)何やってるの 団長!?
ちゃんと反撃して！
Fight back!
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)バンとの戦いでの傷が
響いてるんだ｡
He's still hurt from the fight with Ban.
(ﾊﾞﾝ)そうじゃねぇ｡
わざと やられてんだよ｡
That's not it.
He's taking those hits on purpose.
つまんねぇまねしやがって｡
I can't believe he's being so lame.
Wh-What does that mean?!
ちょっ！ それ どういうこと!?
俺が知ふは…｡
Do I look like Cap'n to you?
Why did you kill the person most important to you?!
なぜ 己の想い人を…➡
Why did you kill Liz?!
リズを殺した!?
(ｹｲﾝ)なぜ 皆を裏切ったんじゃ!?
Why did you betray everyone?!
It's huge!
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)大きい！
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)ダメだ よけて！
No! Dodge it!
守ろうとした｡
全てを守りたかった｡
I wanted to protect them.
I wanted to protect everything.
でも できなかった｡
But...
I couldn't.
それが俺の罪｡
That is my sin.
That's why this time,
だから 今度こそ
守らなきゃならねぇんだ！
I won't fail in protecting them!
Huh? Where'd that huge fireball go?
あれ？ 巨大な火の玉は？
き… 消えた？
I-It disappeared?
Counter Vanish.
｢カウンターバニッシュ｣｡
己に向けられた➡
A technique that disperses any
special power attack directed at you.
あらゆる攻撃魔力を
消失させる技か｡➡
確かに
お前さんは あのメリオダスじゃ｡
There's no mistaking it. You're the Meliodas I know.
あんたのことも思い出したぜ
ケイン＝バルザド｡
I remember you now. You're Cain Barzad.
So it finally came to you.
(ｹｲﾝ)ようやく思い出したか｡
Back when you were a Holy Knight,
you always called yourself "The Flame Barzad."
聖騎士団にいたころは
炎のバルザドって名乗ってたし➡
いっつも 甲冑かぶってたろうが｡
You always used to wear armor, too.
Oh, is that so?
そうじゃったか？
Meliodas, can I believe in the words you just spoke?
メリオダス さっきの言葉を
信じてよいのじゃな？
That you didn't betray Danafor or the people?
ダナフォールを…
皆を裏切っていないと｡
Yeah.
(ｹｲﾝ)うわぁ～… よかった～！➡
I'm so happy!
わしは お前さんの
その言葉が聞きたかったんじゃ｡
I've always wanted to hear those words from you!
バルザド…｡
(ｹｲﾝ)任務から帰ってみれば➡
Barzad...
When I returned from my mission, everything was completely gone.
何もかもが消えうせていて➡
I heard dreadful rumors that you destroyed the Kingdom.
お前さんが
ダナフォールを滅ぼしたと➡
まことしやかな噂が流れた｡
それでも
わしは うそと信じたかった｡
Even so, I wanted them to be lies.
What's going on?
どうなってんの？
さあ…｡
Beats me.
I'm so glad to have the chance to meet another comrade-in-arms from the past like this.
(ｹｲﾝ)本当によかった｡
こうして また 生きて➡
昔の同志に会えたんじゃ｡
(ﾗﾌﾞﾍﾙﾑ)
あ… あの～ 喧嘩の方は…｡
A-About the fight...
It's my loss.
わしの負けじゃ｡
Whoa, what's this? Cain has admitted defeat!
(ﾗﾌﾞﾍﾙﾑ)おっ？ お～っと！
ケイン自ら 負けを認めた｡➡
よって 準決勝 二組目の勝者は
メリオダフ！
Therefore, the winner of the
second semifinal fight is Meliodaz!
You sure?
いいのか？
(ｹｲﾝ)ああ～ いいとも｡➡
Of course!
しかし 相変わらず
甘っちょろい男じゃな｡➡
But you're just as soft and naïve as always.
わしの技を
そのまま はね返せたろうに｡
You should've just reflected all my attacks.
それで あんたが死んじまったら
元も子もねぇだろ｡
But if you had died from that, I would've felt bad.
そこまで老いぼれとらんわ｡➡
I haven't gotten that old yet.
じゃあ わしは
のんびり 決勝を見物するかの｡
Well then, I guess I'll just sit back and enjoy watching the finals!
And now, the moment you've all been waiting for.
(ﾗﾌﾞﾍﾙﾑ)さあ いよいよ
バイゼル喧嘩祭り 決勝戦だ～！➡
The Byzel Fight Festival finals!
We had a parade of monstrous contestants this year.
今年は とんでもねぇヤツらの
オンパレード！➡
その頂点を極める戦いだぞ～！
This is the fight for the top!
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)じゃ ちょっと待っててね｡
Wait up for us, okay?
Hey, we really need to do something about Elizabeth's appearance.
つぅか
エリザベスちゃんの その格好➡
まず なんとかしねぇとな｡
しかたねぇ｡
Guess it's up to me.
Elizabeth, can you raise your arms for just a moment?
エリザベスちゃん
一瞬でいいから 腕を上げてくれ｡
ほっ ほっ！ スポン！
Thank you, Hawk!
ありがとう ホークちゃん｡
What an impressive yet useless skill!
何 この無駄にすごい特技？
Time for both contestants to enter the ring!
(ﾗﾌﾞﾍﾙﾑ)では両者 リングに
上がっちゃってちょうだい！
Well, we're definitely going to get your Sacred Treasure back.
まっ これで
神器の入手は 確定したわけだし➡
適当にやって 終わらせるか｡
Let's just get this over quickly!
My heart has been KO'd by Captain already, though. Just kidding!
僕のハートは もう
団長にＫＯされちゃってるけど｡
な～んて！
≪きゃあ～！➡
≪メリオダフ こっち向いて～！
ん？
Meliodaz! Look over here!
Let's do something naughty, just like the other night!
今夜も また一緒に
いけないことしましょ～｡
Hurry up and beat that musclebound woman, then come play with us!
そんな筋肉女
ギッタギタにしちゃって➡
遊ぼうよ｡
ずる～い！ 私もぉ｡
No fair! What about me?
(ﾗﾌﾞﾍﾙﾑ)お～っと メリオダフに
ピンクの声援！ 羨ましい～｡
Whoa! Meliodaz has some sexy fans! I'm so jealous!
A climax should be exciting.
(ﾊﾞﾝ)
やっぱ 締めは盛り上がんねぇとな｡
It's gone! My purse is gone!
ねぇ！ 俺様のマネー袋が ねぇ！
Well then, let's get started!
(ﾗﾌﾞﾍﾙﾑ)
じゃ そろそろいってみよ！
You...
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)この…｡
ん？
cheater!
浮気者～～‼
ドゴン！
Guila, have we arrived at Byzel yet?
(ｼﾞｪﾘｺ)
ギーラ バイゼルは まだなのか？
We'll be there in a moment. No need to be so anxious.
(ｷﾞｰﾗ)そう興奮しないの ジェリコ｡
もうすぐよ｡
Of course I'm going to be anxious.
(ｼﾞｪﾘｺ)興奮もするさ｡ この魔力を
存分に使えるのだからな｡
I'm itching to use this power to its fullest.
We're going back and forth on a dead-end street, yo
ittari kitari de ikidomari yo
This abandoned dream is a bitter experience, yo
mihatenu yume wa kori gori kori gori yo
After all, this world we live in is transient, yo
shosen konoyo wa ukiyo no sekai
Open up and defy them all to find high spirits, yo
hirakinaoreba NORINORINORINORI yo
High spirits, yo!
NORINORI yo
Throw in the firewood to reignite
maki wo kubero tayasu na sono hi wo
Your blazing passion before it goes out
tsuki ugokasu MONO wa sou kandou sa
The future will be fine as long as it shines brightly
mirai wa tada kagayaite kurete ireba ii’nda
We switched our intense rampage on
bokura wa Gan Gan abare MO-DO
Making seven sounds of thunder
todorokasu Boom Boom nanatsu no oto
Heading toward an ever-bright tomorrow
Rin Rin hikaru ashita e to susumou
We're ready to shoot the place up
bokura wa Bang Bang HAJI ke MO-DO
Jumping here and there as we go
buttobasu Ran Dom SUTAIRU de ikou yo
Shining through like a diamond
Bling Bling hikaru DAIYAMONDO
Let's go, now we can fly high
iku ze Now we can fly high
(ｱﾗﾝ)｢こうして 父の帰りを信じて
二人の子供は暮らしたのでした｣｡
And so, the children believed in the return
of their father and lived happily every after.
The end.
おしまい｡
(鎧巨人)こ… ども…｡
Children...
That's right. The Knight's children.
そう｡ この騎士の子供たち｡
Waiting...
(鎧巨人)ま… ってる…｡
(ｱﾗﾝ)はい｡
Right.
Next Episode's Report
The final round of the Byzel Fight Festival has arrived!
さあ バイゼル喧嘩祭りも
いよいよ決勝！➡
メリオダフ対マトローナ！➡
Meliodaz versus Matrona!
何やら 不穏な空気だぞ～!?➡
You can feel the danger in the air!
一方 こちらは またしても
期待外れの聖騎士ハウザー｡➡
On the other hand, yet again,
we have the disappointing Holy Knight, Hauser!
スケベ発言を連発したうえの
見事な敗退！
On top of making many perverted comments, he suffered a crushing defeat!
違う！ 俺は そんなつもりじゃ…｡
ああ～ 穴があったら入りたい｡
That's not true! That's not what
I meant. I want to hide in a hole!
Super Cycl—
｢スーパーサイクロン｣！
次回 『七つの大罪』
｢戦慄のカノン｣｡
Next time, on The Seven Deadly Sins: "Terrifying Canon."
I beg of you, please don't
destroy the tournament grounds!
(ﾗﾌﾞﾍﾙﾑ)これ以上は
試合会場を壊さないでくれ！
Episode 12
Terrifying Cannon
安倍政権の２年間の評価が問われ
る
第４７回衆議院選挙は､
投票が続いている｡
午後８時に締め切られるが､